Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art registrar's office records, 1869-2013 COR0005.1.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Loans of works of art [legacy series], 1874-1978; Series 3
  - 1968 Out: Walker Art Center, Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 120)
  - 1969 Receipts (In & Out):, 1969 January-1969 December; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 121)
  - 1969 In: Franz Bader Gallery, Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - 1969 In: Clough, Roger, Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 123)
  - 1969 In: Detroit Institute of Arts, Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - 1969 In: Downing, Thomas, Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 125)
  - 1969 In: Estates Gallery, Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 126)
  - 1969 In: Fischbach Gallery, Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 127)
  - 1969 In: George Washington University, Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 128)
  - 1969 In: Kennedy Galleries, Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 129)
  - 1969 In: Felix Landau Gallery, Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 130)
  - 1969 In: Betty Parsons Gallery, Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 131)
  - 1969 In: Reed, Paul, Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 132)
  - 1969 In: Spanierman, Ira, Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 133)
  - 1969 In: Tourigian, Martin, Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - 1969 In: Van Dijk, James, Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 135)
  - 1969 In: Wade Kenneth, Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 136)
  - 1969 Out: American Federation of Arts, Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 137)
  - 1969 Out: Bicentennial Exhibit for Charlotte, N. Carolina, Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 138)
  - 1969 Out: Bowdin College (Museum of Art), Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 139)
  - 1969 Out: Cummer Gallery of Art, Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 140)
  - 1969 Out: International Exhibits Foundation (W.S. Mount Exhibition), Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 141)
  - 1969 Out: Los Angeles County Museum of Art, Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 142)
  - 1969 Out: National Portrait Gallery, Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 143)
  - 1969 Out: Nationalgalerie (Berlin), Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 144)
  - 1969 Out: North Carolina Museum of Art, Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 145)
  - 1969 Out: Smith, Arthur, Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 146)
  - 1969 Out: Smithsonian Institution, Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - 1969 Out: Ternbach, Joseph (For Restoration), Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 148)
  - 1969 Out: University of Kansas (Tourism Tapestry), Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - 1969 Out: University of Nebraska, Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 150)
  - 1969 Out: University of Rochester, Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 151)
  - 1969 Out: Whitney Museum of American Art, 19691; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 152)
  - 1969 Out: Wilderstein & Co. (Citizens Committee for Children), Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 153)
  - 1969 Out: Worcester Art Museum, Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - 1969 Out: WTTG (TV & Radio Station), Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 155)
  - 1970 In: Receipts (TL 1-42), 1970 January-1970 April; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 1970 In: Receipts (TL 43-65), 1970 May-1970 September; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 1970 In: Receipts (TL 66-95), 1970 October; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 1970 In: Receipts (TL 96-111), 1970 November-1970 December; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 1970 Out: Receipts (L 1-9), 1970 January-1970 April; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 1970 Out: Receipts (L 20-32), 1970 May-1970 September; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 1970 Out: Receipts (L 33-40), 1970 October-1970 December; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 1970 Returned Receipts (R 1-33), 1970 January-1970 February; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - 1970 Returned Receipts (R 34-56), 1970 March-1970 June; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - 1970 Returned Receipts (R 57-72), 1970 July-1970 October; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - 1970 Returned Receipts (R 73-88), 1970 November-1970 December; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - 1970 In: A Miscellaneous, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - 1970 In: B-C Miscellaneous, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - 1970 In: D-F Miscellaneous, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - 1970 In: Hartgen, Vincent, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - 1970 In: G-K Miscellaneous, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - 1970 In: L Miscellaneous, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - 1970 In: M-Q Miscellaneous, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - 1970 In: R-V Miscellaneous, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - 1970 In: Washington Room - Artistis A-L, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - 1970 In: Washington Room - Artists M-Z, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - 1970 Out: Allentown Art Museum, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - 1970 Out: Baltimore Museum of Art "Figure in Modern Sculpture Exhibit", Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - 1970 Out: Baltimore Museum of Art "Washington: 20 Years" Exhibition, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - 1970 Out: Leo Castelli Gallery, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - 1970 Out: Colorado Springs Fine Arts Center, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - 1970 Out: Edmonton Art Gallery (Canada), Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - 1970 Out: Everson Museum of Art (Syracuse, NY), Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - 1970 Out: Furman, Arthur (Sacklarian Work), Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - 1970 Out: Gallery of Modern Art (NY), Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - 1970 Out: Houston Museum of Fine Arts, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - 1970 Out: Indiana University Art Museum, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - 1970 Out: Coe Kerr Gallery (NY), Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - 1970 Out: Metropolitan Museum of Art "19th Century America" Exhibition, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - 1970 Out: Metropolitan Museum of Art "The Year 1200" Exhibition, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - 1970 Out: Munson-Williams-Proctor Institute, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - 1970 Out: New Jersey State Museum, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - 1970 Out: Pennsylvania State University, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - 1970 Out: Ringling Museum of Art, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - 1970 Out: Smithsonian Institution - Nat'l Collection of Fine Arts, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - 1970 Out: Smithsonian Institution - Nat'l Gallery of Art, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - 1970 Out: Smithsonian Institution - National Portrait Gallery, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - 1970 Out: University of Maryland, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - 1970 Out: University of Pennsylania, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - 1970 Out: University of Texas / Allentown Art Museum, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - 1970 Out: Walters Art Gallery, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - 1970 Out: White House, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - 1970 Out: Whitney Museum of American Art, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - 1970 Out: Wildenstein & Co. (Degas "The Ballet"), Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - 1971 In: Receipts (TL 112-147), 1971 January-1971 February; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - 1971 In: Receipts (TL 148-182), 1971 March-1971 April; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - 1971 In: Receipts (TL 183-217), 1971 May-1971 September; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - 1971 In: Receipts (TL 218-66, 301-305), 1971 October-1971 December; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - 1971 Out: Receipts (L 41-58), 1971 January-1971 June; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - 1971 Out: Receipts (L 59-70), 1971 July-1971 September; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - 1971 Out: Receipts (L 71, 181-193), 1971 October-1971 December; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - 1971 Return Receipts (R 89-132), 1971 January-1971 April; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - 1971 Return Receipts (R 134-173), 1971 May-1971 June; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - 1971 Return Receipts (R 174-204), 1971 July-1971 October; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - 1971 Return Receipts (R 211-265), 1971 November-1971 December; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - 1971 In: Barron, Florence (Stella Wolrk), Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - 1971 In: A - B Miscellaeous, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - 1971 In: C - D Miscellaneous, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - 1971 In: E - G Miscellaneous, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - 1971 In: H - J Miscellaneous, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - 1971 In: Kainen, Jacob (Pollack Work), Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - 1971 In: K - O Miscellaneous, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - 1971 In: P - S Miscellaneous, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - 1971 In: T - V Miscellaneous, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - 1971 In: Washington Room - Artists A - L, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - 1971 In: Washington Room - Artists M - Z, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - 1971 In: W - Z Miscellaneous, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - 1971 Out: 1971/72 Schedule of Loans, 1971-1972; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - 1971 Out: Albrecht Gallery, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - 1971 Out: Cleveland Museum of Art, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - 1971 Out: Dallas Museum of Fine Arts, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - 1971 Out: High Museum of Art, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - 1971 Out: Kreeger, Dave - Kienholz, Ed "The Birthday" 1968, 1968-1971; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - 1971 Out: Kreeger, Dave - Kienholz, Ed "The Birthday" 1969 (Jan.-Sept.), 1969-1971; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - 1971 Out: Kreeger, Dave - Kienholz, Ed "The Birthday" 1969 (Oct.-Dec..), 1969-1971; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - 1971 Out: Kreeger, Dave - Kienholz, Ed "The Birthday" 1970, 1970-1971; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - 1971 Out: Kreeger, Dave - Kienholz, Ed "The Birthday" 1971 (Jan.-Sept.), 1971 January-1971 September; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - 1971 Out: Kreeger, Dave - Kienholz, Ed "The Birthday" 1971 (Oct.-Dec.), 1971 October-1971 December; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - 1971 Out: Kreeger, Dave - Kienholz, Ed "The Birthday" 1972-1973, 1971-1973; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - 1971 Out: Kreeger, Dave - Kienholz, Ed "The Birthday" Misc. Receipts, Bills, etc., Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - 1971 Out: Meredith J. Long & Co. "Americans at Home & Abroad" Exhibitin, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - 1971 Out: Norman Mackenzie Gallery, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - 1971 Out: Montclair Art Museum, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - 1971 Out: Smithsonian Institution - National Collection of Fine Arts, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - 1971 Out: Smithsonian Institution - National Portrait Gallery, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - 1971 Out: U.S. State Department - Art in Embassies: Ireland (Dublin), Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - 1971 Out: U.S. State Department - Art in Embassies: Peru (Lima), Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 92)
  - 1971 Out: U.S. State Department - Art in Embassies: U.S.S.R. Moscow) 1970, 1970-1971; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 93)
  - 1971 Out: U.S. State Department - Art in Embassies: U.S.S.R. Moscow) 1971 Aug.-Sept., 1971 August-1971 September; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 94)
  - 1971 Out: U.S. State Department - Art in Embassies: U.S.S.R. Moscow) 1971 Oct.-Dec., 1971 October-1971 December; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 95)
  - 1971 Out: U.S. State Department - Art in Embassies: U.S.S.R. Moscow) 1972, 1971-1972; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 96)
  - 1971 Out: U.S. State Department - Art in Embassies: U.S.S.R. Moscow) 1973, 1971-1973; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 97)
  - 1971 Out: U.S. State Department - Washington Office Quarters, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 98)
  - 1971 Out: U.S. State Department - MIscellaneous, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 99)
  - 1971 Out: University of Miami, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 100)
  - 1971 Out: University of Nebraska, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 101)
  - 1971 Out: University of Texas at Austin, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 102)
  - 1971 Out: Washington County Museum of Fine Arts, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 103)
  - 1971 Out: Woodward & Lothrop, Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 104)
  - 1972 In: Receipts (TL 306-44), 1972 January-1972 April; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 105)
  - 1972 In: Receipts (TL 345-75), 1972 May; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 106)
  - 1972 In: Receipts (TL 376-419), 1972 June; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 107)
  - 1972 In: Receipts (TL 420-35), 1972 July; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 108)
  - 1972 In: Receipts (TL 436-55), 1972 August; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 109)
  - 1972 In: Receipts (TL 456-65), 1972 September; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 110)
  - 1972 In: Receipts (TL 466-92), 1972 October; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 111)
  - 1972 In: Receipts (TL 493-534), 1972 November; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 112)
  - 1972 In: Receipts (TL 535-43), 1972 December; Series 3 (Box 6, Folder 113)
  - 1972 Out: Receipts (L Series), 1972 January-1972 March; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 1972 Out: Receipts (L Series), 1972 April-1972 August; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 1972 Out: Receipts (L Series), 1972September-1972 December; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 1972 Returned Receipts (R Series), 1972 January-1972 May; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - 1972 Returned Receipts (R Series), 1972 June-1972 August; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 1972 Returned Receipts (R Series), 1972 September; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - 1972 Returned Receipts (R Series), 1972 October; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - 1972 Returned Receipts (R Series), 1972 November; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - 1972 Returned Receipts (R Series), 1972 December; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - 1972 In: Bacon, Robert Low, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - 1972 In: Bard, Gene, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - 1972 In: Bruno, Frank, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - 1972 In: A - B Miscellaneous, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - 1972 In: Chapin, Aldus, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - 1972 In: Connor, Bruce, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - 1972 In: C- E Miscellaneous, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - 1972 In: Fleischman, Lawrence, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - 1972 In: G Miscellaneous, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - 1972 In: H - J Miscellaneous, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - 1972 In: Kreeger, David Lloyd, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - 1972 In: K - M Miscellaneous, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - 1972 In: N - P Miscellaneous, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - 1972 In: Q - R Miscellaneous, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - 1972 In: S Miscellaneous, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - 1972 In: T - V Miscellaneous, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - 1972 In: Washington Room, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - 1972 In: W - Z Miscellaneous, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - 1972 Out: American University, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - 1972 Out: Boston Museum of Fine Arts / Cincinnati Art Museum, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - 1972 Out: Carnegie Institute, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - 1972 Out: Colorado Springs Fine Arts Center, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - 1972 Out: Houston Museum of Fine Arts / San Francisco Museum of Art, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - 1972 Out: Louvre (Paris, France), Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - 1972 Out: Museum of Contemporary Art (CHicago), Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - 1972 Out: National Park Service (U.S. Interior Dept.), Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - 1972 Out: North Carolina Museum of Art, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - 1972 Out: Pasadena Art Museum / Newport Harbor Art Museum, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - 1972 Out: Phillips Collection, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - 1972 Out: Pointdexter Gallery, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - 1972 Out: Rhode Island School of Design, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - 1972 Out: San Paolo Museum of Art (Wesley Duke Lee Work), Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - 1972 Out: Smithsonian Institution - National Collection of Fine Arts, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - 1972 Out: Smithsonian Institution - National Gallery of Art, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - 1972 Out: Smithsonian Institution - National Portrait Gallery "Also Runs", Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - 1972 Out: Smithsonian Institution - National Portraint Gallery "J.Q. Adams", Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - 1972 Out: Smithsonian Institution - National Portrait Gallery "Old House of Reps." Work, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - 1972 Out: Swift, Carlton B., Jr. - U.S. Embassy: Netherlands, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - 1972 Out: University of Arizona, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - 1972 Out: University of California, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - 1972 Out: University of Michigan, 1872; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - 1972 Out: University of Wisconsin, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - 1972 Out: Walker Art Center, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - 1972 Out: Whitney Museum of American Art, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - 1972 Out: Wildenstein & Co., Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - 1973 In: Receipts (TL 544 -81), 1973 January-1973 February; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - 1973 in: Receipts (TL 582-611), 1973 March; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - 1973 In: Receipts (TL 612-646), 1973 April 1-16; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - 1973 In: Receipts (TL 647-692), 1973 April 17-30; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - 1973 In: Receipts (TL 693-717), 1973 May; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - 1973 In: Receipts (TL 718-731), 1973 June-1973 August; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - 1973 In: Receipts (TL 732-754), 1973 September-1973 October; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - 1973 In: Receipts (TL 755-778), 1973 November-1973 December; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - 1973 Out: Receipts (L 120-143), 1973 January-1973 April; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - 1973 Out: Receipts (L 144-173), 1973 May-1973 December; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - 1973 Returned Receipts (F Series), 1973 January-1973 February; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - 1973 Returned Receipts R Series), 1973 March; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - 1973 Returned Receipts (R Series), 1973 April; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - 1973 Returned Receipts (R Series), 1973 May; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - 1973 Returned Receipts (R Series), 1973 June 1-12; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - 1973 Returned Receipts (R Series), 1973 June 13-30; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - 1973 Returned Receipts (R Series), 1973 July-1973 August; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - 1973 Returned Receipts (R Series), 1973 September-1973 October; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - 1973 Returned Receipts (R Series), 1973 November-1973 December; Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - 1973 In: Beach, Robert O., Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - 1973 In: Borsodi, Ralph W., Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - 1973 In: Bradlee, Antoinette, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - 1973 In: Chilean Embassy, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - 1973 In: A - E Miscellaneous, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - 1973 In: Friends of the Corcoran Dinner - Knight, Love, Stackhouse, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - 1973 In: F Miscellaneous, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - 1973 In: Gallery Marc, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - 1973 In: Henri Gallery, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - 1973 In: Jacobs Ladder Gallery, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - 1973 In: Jefferson Place Gallery (Sheila Isham Work), Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - 1973 In: Kornbee Gallery, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - 1973 In: Kreeger, David Lloyd, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - 1973 In: Lerner, Marilyn, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - 1973 In: Ludlow, Mrs. William G., Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - 1973 In: Parke-Bernet Galleries, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - 1973 In: Pyramid Galleries, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - 1973 In: Smithsonian Institute - Nat'l Portrait Gallery, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - 1973 In: O - S Miscellaneous, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - 1973 In: Truitt, Ann, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - 1973 In: University of Pennsylvania, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - 1973 In: Van Dijk, James, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - 1973 In: Washington Room - Artists A - Z, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - 1973 In: Wofford, Philip, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - 1973 In: Wolf, Tom, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - 1973 In: Woodward Foundation, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - 1973 In: Woodward, Mrs. Robert F., Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - 1973 In: W MIscellaneous, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - 1973 Out: Amon Carter Museum of Western Art, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - 1973 Out: Boston Museum of Fine Arts, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - 1973 Out: Brooklyn Museum, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - 1973 Out: Columbia Art Museum / Univ. of South Carolina, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - 1973 Out: Wm. A. Farnsworth Library & Art Museum, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 106)
  - 1973 Out: High Museum of Art (Atlanta, GA), Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 107)
  - 1973 Out: Mobile Art Gallery, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 108)
  - 1973 Out: Munson-Williams-Proctor Institute, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 109)
  - 1973 Out: Museum of Contemporary Art - Chicago, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 110)
  - 1973 Out: R. W. Norton Art Gallery (LA), Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 111)
  - 1973 Out: Pennsylvania Academy of Fine Arts, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 112)
  - 1973 Out: Rhode Island School of Design, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 113)
  - 1973 Out: Smithsonian Institution - Nat'l Collection of Fine Arts "Diffusion of Style ...", Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 114)
  - 1973 Out: Smithsonian Institution - Nat'l Collection of Fine Arts "Venice Biennale", Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 115)
  - 1973 Out: Smithsonian Institution - Nat'l Gallery of Art, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 116)
  - 1973 Out: State University of N.Y. - Albany, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 117)
  - 1973 Out: Textile Museum, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 118)
  - 1973 Out: University of Arizona, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 119)
  - 1973 Out: University of Kentucky, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 120)
  - 1973 Out: University of Minnesota, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 121)
  - 1973 Out: University of New Mexico, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 122)
  - 1973 Out: Valparaiso Muncipal Museum of Art (Chile), Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 123)
  - 1973 Out: Whitney Museum of American Art - "Bierstadt Retrospective", Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 124)
  - 1973 Out: Whitney Museum of American Art '"Winsolw Homer", Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 125)
  - 1973 Out: Worcester Art Museum, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 126)
  - 1974 In: Receipts (TL Series 779-810), 1974 January-1974 May; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 1974 In: Receipts (TL Series 813-838), 1974 June-1974 October; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 1974 In: Receipts (TL 839-48), 1974 November-1974 December; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 1974 Out: Receipts (L Series), 1974 January-1974 May; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - 1974 Out: Receipts (L Series), 1974 June-1974 September; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - 1974 Out: Receipts (L Series), 1974 October-1974 December; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - 1974 Receipts Returned: 19th Area Exhibition R Series 828-54, 1974 November; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - 1974 Receipts Returned: 19th Area Show R Series 855-79, Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 1974 Receipts Returned: 19th Area Show R Series 880-97, Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 1974 Receipts Returned: 19th Area Show R Series 298-319, Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 1974 Receipts Returned: 19th Area Show R Series 320-334, Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - 1974 Receipts Returned: 19th Area Show R Series 335-53, Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - 1974 Receipts Returned: R Series 753-776, 1974 January-1974 April; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - 1974 Receipts Returned: R Series 777-810, 1974 May-1974 July; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - 1974 Receipts Returned: R Series 811-37, 1974 August-1974 December; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - 1974 In: Cybis Porcelain Studio, Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - 1974 In: George Washington University, Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - 1974 In: L - M Miscellaneous, Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - 1974 In: Betty Parsons Gallery, Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - 1974 In: Protetch, Max, Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - 1974 In: Visby, Borge, Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - 1974 In: Wade, Kenneth, Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - 1974 In: Williams, Herman Warner, Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - 1974 Out: Albright-Knox Art Gallery, Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - 1974 Out: Baltimore Museum of Art "Theodore Robinson" Exhibit, Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - 1974 Out: Baltimore Museum of Art "Grace Turnbull" Exhibit, Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - 1974 Out: Boston Museum of Fine Arts, Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - 1974 Out: Chevy Chase Savings & Loan, Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - 1974 Out: Finch College Museum of Art, Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - 1974 Out: International Exhibitions Foundation "Amer. Portraits" Exhibition, Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 30)